Register to The E.Y. Harburg Collection
Yale University Music Library
- Writings, 1929-1968; Series I; 20 boxes
  - Writings: Lyrics, Libretti, and Scores
    - The Happiest Girl in the World (N.Y. opening: Martin Beck Theatre, 1961 Apr 3; book by Fred Saidy & Henry Myers; lyrics by E.Y. Harburg to music by Offenbach.)
      - Lyrics & Scores: "Lysistrata" [Early version]
        - "The Happiest Girl in the World" (Box 12, Folder 69)
          Typed lyrics, 2 versions with holograph corrections -- 1 page each
          Typed lyrics with vocal parts carbon copy ["The Happiest Man in the World"]-- 2 pages
          Holograph notes & lyrics, in pencil -- 18 pages
        - "The Lonesomest Girl in the World" (reprise) (Box 12, Folder 69)
          Typed lyrics, with holograph corrections, with parts -- 1 page
          Typed lyrics, photocopy -- 1 page
          Piano-vocal score ["The Happiest Man in the World"] with lyrics, adaptation by Gorney from Offenbach's La Perichole, photostatic copy of handwritten score -- 4 pages
        - "The Greek Marine Hymn" (Box 12, Folder 70)
          Typed lyrics, 3 versions -- 1 page each
          Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 3 pages
        - "Shall We Say Farewell" (Box 12, Folder 71)
          Typed lyrics, 2 copies -- 2 pages each
          Holograph draft lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 20 pages
          Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's Orpheus], handwritten in pencil -- 5 pages
          Photostatic copy of above -- 5 pages
        - "Never Be-Devil the Devil" (Box 12, Folder 72)
          Typed lyrics, 3 versions -- 2 pages, 2 pages, 1 page
          Photocopy of typed lyrics -- 1 page
          Holograph draft notes & lyrics -- 21 pages
          Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from "Duo d'Alsace" in Offenbach's Lischen et Fritzchen], handwritten in pencil -- 5 pages
        - "Pluto" [not used] (Box 12, Folder 72)
          Typed patter lyrics -- 2 pages
        - "Whatever That May Be" (Box 12, Folder 73)
          Typed lyrics, 3 versions -- 3 pages, 2 pages, 2 pages
          Holograph lyrics & notes, in ink & pencil -- 24 pages
          Vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney from Offenbach's La Belle Hélène, handwritten in ink – 2 pages
          Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney from Offenbach's La Belle Hélène, handwritten in pencil -- 2 pages
        - "Eureka" (Box 12, Folder 74)
          Typed lyrics with holograph corrections, 2 versions -- 2 pages each
          Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 7 pages
          Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's Bluebeard], handwritten in pencil -- 5 pages
        - "The Oath" (Box 12, Folder 75)
          Typed lyrics -- 2 pages
          Holograph draft lyrics in ink & pencil -- 34 pages
          Piano-vocal score, no lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's Orpheus], handwritten in pencil -- 3 pages
        - "Vive la Virtue" (Box 12, Folder 76)
          "Vive la Virtue" reprise [Act I, last scene], typed lyrics -- 1 page
          "Vive la Virtue" reprise [Act I, last scene], typed lyrics with holograph corrections, carbon -- 2 pages
          Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 14 pages
        - "Adrift on a Star" (Barcarolle) (Box 12, Folder 77)
          Typed lyrics, with parts -- 2 pages
          Holograph draft lyrics in ink & pencil -- 21 pages
          Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's Tales of Hoffmann], handwritten in pencil, 2 different versions -- 3 pages, 4 pages
          Photostatic copy of 2nd piano-vocal score version -- 4 pages
        - "That'll Be the Day", 19 pages (Box 12, Folder 78)
          Holograph draft lyrics, in ink
        - "How Soon, Oh Moon" (Box 12, Folder 78)
          Holograph draft lyrics, in ink -- 7 pages
        - "Lovesick Serenade" (The Shepherd Song) [Also earlier version: "Simple Serenade"] (Box 12, Folder 78)
          Typed lyrics & carbon copy -- 2 pages each
          Holograph draft lyrics in ink & pencil -- 20 pages
        - "Five Minutes of Spring" (Box 12, Folder 79)
          Typed lyrics, 3 versions -- 2 pages, 1 page, 1 page
          Photocopy of typed lyrics with parts -- 1 page
        - At Citadel: "Five Minutes of Spring" Reprise [not used in N.Y.] (Box 12, Folder 79)
          Typed lyrics, 2 versions -- 1 page each
          Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's La Belle Hélène], 4 versions and photostatic copy, handwritten in pencil -- 4 pages, 3 pages, 3 pages, 3 pages
        - "Never Trust a Virgin" (Box 12, Folder 80)
          Typed lyrics, 2 different copies -- 4 pages, 2 pages
          Photocopy of typed lyrics -- 2 pages
          Holograph draft lyrics & notes, in ink & pencil -- 21 pages
        - [Entrance of the Courtesans] (incidental music), 2 pages (Box 12, Folder 80)
          Piano-vocal score, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's Tales of Hoffmann], handwritten in pencil
        - "Hup-Two-Three" [used only in New Haven] (Box 12, Folder 81)
          Holograph draft lyrics in ink -- 2 pages
        - "Honestly" [used in New Haven] (Box 12, Folder 81)
          Typed lyrics with parts -- 1 page
          Holograph draft notes and lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 13 pages
          Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's The Grand Duchess], handwritten in pencil -- 3 pages
          Piano-vocal score (different arrangement of same lyrics & melody), negative photostat -- 3 pages
        - Unused songs [many written for earlier versions]
          - "Do You See What I See?" (Box 13, Folder 82)
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 8 pages
          - "Excuse My Laughter" (Box 13, Folder 82)
            Typed lyrics, 3 versions -- 2 pages, 3 pages, 3 pages
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 21 pages
            Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney from [Offenbach's Orpheus], handwritten in pencil -- 5 pages
          - ["Chic, Chic, Chic Are We" or "Little Old Gahenna"] (Box 13, Folder 83)
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 32 pages
          - "Lament", 3 pages (Box 13, Folder 83)
            Piano-vocal score, no lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's Tales of Hoffmann], handwritten in pencil
          - "My Mind Says 'Don't' (My Heart Says 'Do')" (Box 13, Folder 83)
            Photocopy of typed lyrics with vocal cues -- 1 page
            Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's La Vie Parisienne?], handwritten, in pencil -- 6 pages
          - "Never Trust a Poet" (Box 13, Folder 84)
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, In ink & pencil -- 32 pages
          - "Politics" (Box 13, Folder 84)
            Piano-vocal score, no lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's La Vie Parisienne?], handwritten, in pencil -- 2 pages
          - "Rhodope's Tavern" (incidental music), 3 pages (Box 13, Folder 84)
            Piano score, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's Orpheus, in pencil]
          - ["Sabre Song"], 5 pages (Box 13, Folder 85)
            Holograph draft lyrics, in ink & pencil
          - ["Scratch a Wife and Find a Doll"], 10 pages (Box 13, Folder 85)
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil
          - "Strategy" [Rewritten verses used in "Whatever May Be" & "The Oath"] (Box 13, Folder 85)
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 16 pages
            Piano-vocal score, with lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach's La Vie Parisienne, Act IV], handwritten in pencil -- 3 pages
            Piano-vocal score, no lyrics, adapted by Gorney, handwritten, in pencil -- 6 pages
          - ["We're Off to the Races"], 3 pages (Box 13, Folder 86)
          - "When Your Heart is Too Young" (Box 13, Folder 86)
            Typed lyrics with holograph additions -- 3 pages
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 10 pages
            Piano-vocal score with lyrics, adapted by Gorney [from Offenbach unidentified source], handwritten, in pencil -- 7 pages
          - "Where Have I Heard That Song Before?", 16 pages (Box 13, Folder 87)
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in pencil
          - "Who Needs a Woman?" (Box 13, Folder 87)
            Typed lyrics, carbon copy -- 1 page
            Typed lyrics, including reprise, carbon copy -- 1 page
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 13 pages
      - Notes (Box 13, Folder 88)
        Commentaries on rehearsals [from E.Y. Harburg to Cyril Ritchard & Lee Guber during Philadelphia try-out], typed, carbon copy -- 3 pages, 4 pages
        Notes from E.Y. Harburg to Cyril Ritchard [about N.Y. production?], typed -- 3 pages
        "Scholarly Note," typed, carbon paper, initialed (BD) -- 1 page
        Miscellaneous notes for "Orpheus," "Lysistrata," The Happiest Girl, holograph in ink & pencil -- 49 pages
        List of musical numbers, typed, carbon copy -- 1 page
        Leadsheet for "Shall We Say Farewell," "Honestly" & "Five Minutes of Spring," handwritten, in pencil -- 3 pages
        Unidentified piano-vocal score, incomplete, handwritten, in pencil -- 3 pages
      - Complete original conductor's score with lyrics (N.Y. Opening, 269 pages (Box 13, Folder 89)
        Includes production & casting information
    - Gay Purree (Warner Bros.-UPA animated film, 1962; music & lyrics by Harold Arlen & E.Y. Harburg)
      - "Mewsette" (Box 14, Folder 90)
        Typed lyrics, carbon copy, with holograph revisions -- 3 pages
        Piano-vocal score with lyrics, copyist's manuscript -- 4 pages
        Interlude: piano-vocal score with lyrics, copyist's manuscript -- 4 pages
        Holograph draft lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 23 pages
      - "Little Drops of Rain" (Box 14, Folder 91)
        Piano-vocal score with lyrics, copyist's manuscript -- 3 pages
        Holograph draft lyrics, in pencil [On verso: lyrics for "Unusual Weather"?] -- 1 page
      - "The Money Cat" (Box 14, Folder 92)
        Typed lyrics, carbon copy, with holograph revisions -- 1 page
        Piano-vocal score with lyrics, copyist's manuscript -- 6 pages
        Holograph draft lyrics in ink & pencil -- 4 pages
      - "Take My Hand, Paree" (Box 14, Folder 93)
        "Mlle. Renard's Introduction to Song": piano-vocal score with lyrics, copyist's manuscript -- 3 pages
        Holograph draft lyrics & notes, in ink & pencil -- 7 pages
      - "Paris Is a Lonely Town" (Box 14, Folder 94)
        Piano-vocal score with lyrics, copyist's manuscript -- 5 pages
        Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in pencil -- 6 pages
      - "Bubbles" (Box 14, Folder 95)
        Typed lyrics, carbon copy, with holograph corrections -- 3 pages
        Piano-vocal score with lyrics, copyist's manuscript -- 7 pages
      - "Roses Red, Violets Blue" (Box 14, Folder 96)
        Piano-vocal score with lyrics, copyists's manuscript (includes interlude) -- 4 pages
      - "The Horse Won't Talk" (Box 14, Folder 97)
        Holograph draft notes & lyrics -- 1 page
      - "Free At Last" (incidental music), 3 pages (Box 14, Folder 98)
        Piano-vocal score with lyrics, copyist's manuscript
      - ["Bon Jour Amour"] [not used], 7 pages (Box 14, Folder 98)
      - Miscellaneous holograph notes, in ink & pencil, 10 pages (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - Stage Door (British film, 1966)
      - "I Could Go On Singing" (E.Y. Harburg-Arlen; written for Judy Garland), 6 pages (Box 14, Folder 99)
        Holograph draft lyrics & notes in ink & pencil
    - Darling of the Day (N.Y. opening: George Abbott Theatre, 1968 Jan 27; music & lyrics by Jule Styne & E.Y. Harburg)
      - "Buried Alive" (early title taken from the novel by Arnold Bennett on which the musical is based) (Box 14, Folder 100)
        E.Y. Harburg's story outline, typed draft with holograph additions, carbon copy -- 6 pages
        Final typed draft -- 5 pages
        Scene breakdown, typed draft, carbon copy -- 5 pages
        Typed draft with titles of music numbers inserted & holograph additions -- 6 pages
      - "The Great Adventure" (another pre-Broadway title)
        - Story outline by Sam Behrman, E.Y. Harburg & Albee Marre, typed draft, carbon copy -- 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 100)
        - Breakdown of musical numbers, typed, carbon copy, 3 pages (Box 14, Folder 100)
        - Complete typed script in 2 acts; book By Keith Waterhouse & Wills Hall, lyrics by E.Y. Harburg: Act I (1965 May 10), 67 pages; Act II (1965 May 7), 35 pages (Box 14, Folder 101)
        - Copy of typed script for Act I of Waterhouse-Hall book, 67 pages (Box 14, Folder 102)
        - Revised typed script for Act I (E.Y. Harburg note: "July 1965, last version by Keith Waterhouse"), 59 pages (Box 14, Folder 103)
        - Another revised version of Act I of Waterhouse-Hall script, typed, carbon copy [pages 1-5 missing], 56 pages (Box 14, Folder 104)
      - "Buried Alive" (Box 15, Folder 105)
        Typed script for Act I, scenes 1-3, author unidentified [1966 Feb 12] -- 14 pages
        Typed script for Act I, Scene 11 (1966 Mar 11), 5 pages; Scene 12 (1966 Mar 15), 6 pages
        Enclosure: holograph letter to E.Y. Harburg, signed by Sam N. Behrman -- 1 page
      - "Buried Alive" [early version] (Box 15, Folder 106)
        Sections of typed script, photocopies:
        Act I, Scene 6 -- 5 pages
        Act I, Scene 7 -- 1 page
        Act I, Scene 11 -- 3 pages
        Act I, Scene 12 -- 3 pages
        Act II, Scene 1 -- 7 pages
        Act II, Scene 2 -- 5 pages
        Act II, Scene 2 (pages 4-5 revised) -- 2 pages
        Act II, Scene 3 -- 3 pages
        Act II, Scene 4 -- 2 pages
        Act II, Scene 5 -- 4 pages
        Act II, Scene 6 -- 7 pages
        Miscellaneous fragments of script, holograph draft, in ink & pencil -- 9 pages
      - "The Great Adventure" synopsis (E.Y. Harburg note: "Yip Harburg version of how Darling of the Day should have been"), typed, carbon copy, 8 pages (Box 15, Folder 106)
      - Darling of the Day Typed script, Act I, photocopy (E.Y. Harburg note: "Version by Nunnally Johnson"), 65 pages (Box 15, Folder 107)
      - Darling of the Day (Box 15, Folder 108)
        Scene breakdown, typed, photocopy -- 5 pages
        Typed script, Act I -- 79 pages
        Typed script, Act II -- 39 pages
      - Darling of the Day Revised script by Nunnally Johnson, Act I only, typed with holograph comments in margins, 87 pages (Box 15, Folder 109)
        [See also: correspondence with Schenker, Series II, Box 21, Folder 170]
      - "Married Alive" (Toronto production, 1967 Dec 4-16)
        - Rehearsal script, with holograph revisions (Nunnally Johnson book), 155 pages (Box 15, Folder 110)
        - Revisions to Toronto script (Box 15, Folder 111)
          Typed, carbon copies unless otherwise noted:
          Act I, Scene 1 (1967 Dec 8) -- 7 pages
          Act I, Scene 1 (1967 Dec 17) -- 4 pages
          Act I, Scene 3 (1967 Dec 14) -- 2 pages
          Act I, Scene 3 (1967 Dec 16) -- 4 pages
          Act I, Scene 3 [1967 Dec 26] -- 2 pages
          Act I, Scene 3, holograph, in ink [no date] -- 6 pages
          Act I, Scene 3 [no date] -- 4 pages
          Act I, Scene 8, photostat [1967 Dec 8] -- 2 pages
          Act I, Scene 9 [no date] -- 6 pages
          Act I, Scene 13, photostat [1967 Dec 15] -- 5 pages
          Act I, Scene 13, with holograph additions (1967 Dec 19) -- 2 pages
          Act II, Scenes 1-3 [no date] -- 7 pages
          Act II, Scene 4, photostat [no date] -- 8 pages
        - "Married Alive" script by Nunnally Johnson, including lyrics, Act I only, photostatic copy, 72 pages (Box 16, Folder 112)
        - Character sketch of Alice (E.Y. Harburg note: "as guide to lyrics for her"), typed, 2 pages (Box 16, Folder 112)
        - Open letter from E.Y. Harburg to "Colleagues of MARRIED (and I hope ALIVE);" typed recommendations for changes to show [1967?], 16 pages (Box 16, Folder 112)
        - Production staff list for Darling of the Day, typed, 2 pages (Box 16, Folder 112)
        - Musical numbers for Broadway production
          (Copyist's scores are photostatic copies, unless noted otherwise)
          - "I'm Mad for Art"
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, 2 copies -- 8 pages each
            Lyrics & patter, typed, carbon copy -- 2 pages
            Holograph draft lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 4 pages
          - "He's a Genius"
            Typed lyrics, final version -- 4 pages
            Typed lyrics, earlier version, carbon copy -- 1 page
          - "To Get Out of This World Alive"
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics -- 8 pages
            Typed lyrics, final version -- 2 pages
            Typed lyrics, with dialogue, photostatic copy -- 2 pages
            Typed draft lyrics with dialogue, carbon copy -- 2 pages
            Holograph draft lyrics & notes, in ink & pencil -- 24 pages
          - "It's Enough to Make a Lady Fall in Love"
            Reprise: copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, 3 copies -- 4 pages each
            Published piano-vocal score with lyrics -- 5 pages
            Published piano-vocal score with lyrics, typed
            Final draft including "Double Soliloquy" Reprise -- 5 pages
            Draft of "Double Soliloquy" Reprise -- 1 page
            Earlier version, carbon copy -- 3 pages
            1965 Apr 8 revision, photostatic copy -- 3 pages
            1967 Oct 31 revision, photostatic copy with holograph corrections -- 2 pages
            Reprise: 1967 Oct 25 revision, photostatic copy with holograph addition -- 2 pages
          - "A Gentleman's Gentleman" [Original "Where Would Britain Be Without a Butler?" used in Toronto production & later revised for N.Y. production]
            "Where Would Britain Be Without a Butler?" Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, 3 copies -- 4 pages each
            "A Gentleman's Gentleman" Typed final draft lyrics -- 5 pages
            "Where Would Britain Be Without a Butler?"
            Typed final draft lyrics -- 1 page
            1965 May 27 revision with holograph additions, photostatic copy -- 1 page
            Typed draft, carbon copy, with holograph additions -- 2 pages
            1965 May 17 revision, typed carbon copy with holograph revisions -- 2 pages
          - "Let's See What Happens"
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, 3 copies -- 5 pages each
            Lyrics: Final typed draft -- 1 page
            Lyrics: Typed draft -- 1 page
            Lyrics: 1965 Apr 15 revision -- 1 page
            Lyrics: 1965 Apr 8 revision -- 1 page
            Lyrics: Typed draft, carbon copy, with holograph corrections -- 1 page
          - "Panache"
            Final typed draft -- 3 pages
            Holograph draft lyrics & notes in ink & pencil -- 18 pages
          - "I've Got a Rainbow Working for Me"
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, 3 copies -- 8 pages each
            Incomplete copy of score -- 4 pages
            Published piano-vocal score with lyrics -- 7 pages
            Final draft -- 3 pages
            1967 Oct 25 revisions with holograph corrections -- 2 pages
            1965 Apr 8 revisions with holograph corrections -- 2 pages
            Draft, carbon copy, with holograph corrections & additions -- 2 pages
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 11 pages
          - "Money, Money, Money"
            Final typed draft lyrics -- 3 pages
            Holograph draft notes, in ink -- 5 pages
          - "That Something Extra Special" [earlier version: "A Little Extra Shilling"]
            Final typed lyrics -- 2 pages
          - "What Makes a Marriage Merry?"
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, 2 copies -- 10 pages each
            Reprise: copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics -- 6 pages
            1965 Apr 15 revision with holograph corrections -- 2 pages
            Holograph draft lyrics & notes, in ink & pencil -- 17 pages
          - "Not On Your Nellie"
            Final draft (all vocal parts) -- 6 pages
            Draft -- 1 page
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 25 pages
          - "Under the Sunset Tree"
            Final draft -- 1 page
            Draft with holograph corrections -- 1 page
            Draft, carbon copy, with holograph corrections -- 1 page
            1967 Oct 10 revisions -- 1 page
            1967 May 27 revisions, carbon copy, with holograph additions -- 1 page
          - "Butler in the Abbey"
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, 3 copies -- 10 pages each
            Draft with corrections, includes vocal cues -- 4 pages
            Draft with vocal cues, carbon copy -- 5 pages
            Draft -- 2 pages
            1965 Jun 11 revision, carbon copy -- 1 page
            1965 May 5 revisions, includes 2nd chorus, carbon copy -- 1 page
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 9 pages
          - "The Darling of the Day" [used in Act I, Scene 3 of Toronto production; not used in N.Y. production]
            Typed lyrics, from script, photocopy -- 1 page
            Typed lyrics, 1965 Apr 8 revision -- 1 page
            Typed lyrics, carbon copy with holograph corrections -- 1 page
            Reprises: "Henry Leek is the Darling of the Day" -- Typed lyrics -- 1 page
            Reprises: "Priam Farrl" or "Leek's Lament" -- Typed lyrics -- 1 page -- Typed lyrics, carbon copy -- 1 page -- Typed lyrics first 2 verses only -- 1 page
          - "Lying in State" [incidental music, used only in Toronto production]
            Copyist's piano score -- 2 pages
          - "A Blushing Bride" [used only in Toronto production]
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, includes patter, 2 copies -- 5 pages each
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics -- 4 pages
            Lyrics: 1967 Oct 25 revision, typed, photocopy -- 1 page
            Lyrics: 1965 May 27 revision, typed photocopy -- 1 page
            Lyrics: 1965 May 14 revision, with holograph additions -- 1 page
          - "Putney on Thames" [used only in Toronto production]
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, 2 photocopies -- 6 pages each
            Lyrics: Typed final draft -- 2 pages
            Lyrics: 1965 Apr 19 revision, photocopy -- 2 pages
            Reprise (Bazaar Scene), typed lyrics, photocopy -- 1 page
          - "I'm Simpally Mad for Bones" [used only in Toronto production]
            Copyist's piano-vocal score with lyrics, different last verse -- 11 pages
            Lyrics: Typed draft with holograph corrections -- 2 pages
            Lyrics: Carbon copy of typed draft with vocal cues & holograph additions -- 3 pages
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 27 pages
          - "Stranger in Your Eyes" [used only in Toronto production]
            Holograph draft lyrics in pencil -- 5 pages
          - "Come Back to God (Me)" [not used]
            Lyrics: Typed draft with holograph additions -- 1 page
            Lyrics: 1965 May 27 typed draft, incomplete, carbon copy -- 1 page
            Holograph draft notes & lyrics, in ink & pencil -- 5 pages
          - "Don't Pour the Thames into the Rhine" [not used]
            Lyrics: 1965 May 14 typed revision, photocopy -- 1 page
          - "Isn't This a Day!" [not used]
            Holograph draft lyrics, in pencil -- 9 pages
        - Miscellaneous holograph notes & lyrics for song ideas ["Great Adventure," "Enchanté," "Somewhere Over the Hill of Summertime," "I Like It Like It Is"], patter & libretti, 22 pages (Box 17, Folder 133)
        - Notes & suggestions made during rehearsals & tryouts (Box 17, Folder 134)
          Holograph notes, in ink -- [no date] -- 3 pages